I am so freaking excited.
I think this is the best content
we've ever filmed.
By the end of today,
someone's gonna win this $5,000,000.
A show this massive,
let's finish this out strong.
We got a hell of a season.
All our camera crew, turn around.
We're clearing everybody.
They got blindfolds.
What about this BTS crew?
They got cameras everywhere.
Our BTS crew is one of the few
who knows who won.
-All right, here we go.
-Heads up.
You will be taking turns kicking balls
at each other's hearts.
Kick for Hannah.
We're all kicking for Hannah.
It is a sucky feeling,
the entire cast gang up against you.
If your heart is smashed,
you will be eliminated.
This could be the kill shot.
Look how big the studio is.
We're all running on adrenaline.
I'm tired as hell.
I'm worried in the cut
I'm gonna look sleepy.
Start the money counter!
$600,000 and nobody's taking the bribes.
They're nervous. It is what it is.
That's a lot of money.
My life is on the line.
Things are feeling a bit tense.
A lot of these people
will leave with nothing.
Do you get emotional at moments like this?
Three, two, one...
-Somebody pressed it?
-Yeah.
Someone pressed it.
Sorry, bro. Nothing personal.
I owe you my life in this game.
Two people, one shot.
We officially have the winner
of Season 2 of Beast Games!
I am so freaking excited.
A, because I think this is
the best content we have ever filmed,
and B, I just wanna sleep in a bed.
Let's wrap it up.
Are you starting to sleep?
No.
My heart is beating too fast.
This is the actual $5,000,000 check.
And I'm signing right here?
All right.
By the end of today,
someone's gonna win this $5,000,000.
This is what they win, not that cash.
They would get robbed if I gave them cash.
When we film,
it will be a cleared lockdown,
no feeds on the outside.
There will be nobody hanging out here.
With a show this massive,
we really need to keep the integrity
of who and what ends up happening
in this episode.
So let's finish this out strong,
'cause we got a hell of a season.
Okay everybody,
we're closing doors between sets.
We're closing the doors between sets.
-Last day.
-Game day, baby.
Lock in on your verbiage.
Can you please read that?
We should go through it.
This is the grand finale.
We want to build up what's happened,
so these are detailed notes of everything
each contestant so far has done.
I'm just editing them
because this is a lot of word vomit.
You think you have the individual talents
to bring it home?
Yeah, see that's too much.
We have their entire story,
every single episode.
Yeah, very important.
It's like, "You got through the Smart Game
at this time."
And just build up your tone
as you get to the end.
"All bringing you
to this moment right here."
We're good to bring in the contestants
if everyone's quiet.
-Does this give you guys PTSD?
-Yeah.
Yes, it definitely does.
All right, Darius,
lock in when we're done.
Let's do it.
Things are getting set, we're about to get
started with Episode 10, the big finale.
It's go time.
So far in this season, after each game,
we started a timer.
But for this game,
we're gonna jump right into it.
Open the door!
Welcome to the grand finale
where one of you is gonna be winning
that $5,000,000, right here, right now.
You'll be taking turns kicking balls
at each other's hearts.
If your heart is smashed,
you will be eliminated.
We're right below the set
of the first game of the finale.
The hearts are over there,
the contestants are over there
and things are feeling a bit tense
because a lot of these people
will leave with nothing
and one will leave with $5,000,000.
All right, here we go.
Tyler, when you are ready,
kick that ball at whatever heart you want.
I thought that hit it.
Tyler's getting serious!
Look at that face.
He does not like that.
Things are getting good.
Everything just went silent
and Jack is the first one
to be eliminated.
Emotions are at an all-time high.
That is literally
the worst feeling in the world.
Jack, it was nothing personal, buddy.
I honestly mean that.
You can say that all you want,
but when the kick
goes right to your heart...
Don't be crying when you say it.
-Drop him.
-Hit me.
How about that? Five contestants remain,
one of which will win
that $5,000,000 over there.
Kind of went through the stages of grief
very quickly.
When I look back on the show,
hopefully I'm not gonna think about
that moment too much.
But I'm gonna look back on
making it far enough
to give the opportunity to my mom
and my brother to come out here
and share that moment with me.
Having made it so far,
I hope they're proud of me.
We still need to eliminate
one more of you.
Brett, when you're ready.
It almost hit Cory!
Kick for Hannah.
We're all kicking for Hannah.
It is a sucky feeling, to have
the entire cast gang up against you.
This could be it.
This could be the kill shot.
Come on.
We have the greatest episode of all time,
but are you out of your... What just...
That was incredible.
The first time he targets Auguste,
Auguste is out.
I'm sorry, bro.
Auguste, to me, like,
was the best student of the game.
And I thought he would make it
to the final two.
So to see him go out like this,
by one of his friends,
seeing an alliance break
the last second like that
is just devestating.
I don't know why that had to happen
that way.
We went through the whole game together.
That was the last thing I was expecting.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why you did that.
I'm in shock.
It's on your cue.
Drop him.
Never would have thought
that would happen.
That's his alliance member.
He just turned on him
and hit him, first try.
I can't believe it.
I cannot believe it.
I've never seen anything like it.
-Sorry, bro.
-Appreciate you, bro.
What's gonna affect you a lot
is walking away with nothing.
The 41 days, the sacrifice,
the waste of time, all that.
-Just know, man...
-This was 100% worth it.
-I'm just like…
-There...
Tyler, he's someone
who I've been close with.
Pretty much every bus ride
we sat next to each other.
He's the last person
I thought would go for me.
And like that, when it's the closest
person to you on stage
and so that just stinks.
Auguste was a close friend of mine,
he still is.
But he was a big threat too,
so it was a strategic play.
What really got me to change my mind
was seeing Hannah in tears.
A lot of us were going for her.
I wouldn't want my boys at home
to gang up on someone.
When it was everyone coming for me,
it just made me feel very alone.
And it is a game, and I get it.
But that was the hard part for me.
How are we looking on cameras?
How long do we need?
I say we proceed to the next game
and eliminate another one of you.
The drone is up.
They're about to play the second game.
It's a combination of Strong and Smart.
We'll see how long
they can hold onto the pole
and if they can memorize the blocks.
First person to touch their button
will bring the platforms up
and have to come over here
and solve the 16-block pattern
from memory.
If you rebuild it incorrectly,
you will be eliminated.
Oh, my God.
Drop their platforms!
The game is on!
You're good. You can step off.
Come over, Brett.
So far, he's doing it from his own memory.
No one's helped him.
Hey, Russ, if it's right, turn it green,
if it's wrong, turn it red. That's it.
All right. It is officially locked in.
He did it!
Brett has now guaranteed a spot
in the top three.
Now you three are on the chopping block.
I can tell Brett is already stressed.
But it's not official
until he smashes your heart.
You have to drop it.
In front of the person.
Dude, really?
I am so sorry, but Hannah,
I am going to pick you.
Obviously I'm heartbroken to be
about to be dropped to my death,
but I feel okay leaving with
this combination of people.
All right, whenever you're ready, Brett.
All right, drop her.
I'm honestly in shock. How did I make it
to the top four of Beast Games Season 2?
How was I the final female,
the final Smart person?
That doesn't feel real.
When I applied, I was like,
"Try not to be in the first 50% out."
How did I get here? I don't understand.
-For old times' sake.
-For old times' sake, get this...
I didn't go limp, I'm sorry.
You good?
For old times' sake.
All right, let's do it.
We're about to eliminate one more of you.
Welcome to the final bribe.
We're working even later into the night,
but we finally started our third game,
and that's the bribe.
One of them could walk away
with $1,000,000 if they self-eliminate.
Cuff them!
I just handcuffed you. React to that.
I feel trapped right now.
-Are you content with how they're...
-They're nervous. It is what it is.
It's not a YouTube, so I'm not gonna...
We're already at the point where
we're forcing it,
-so let's just let them be them.
-Perfect.
Start the money counter!
Let's see what your price is.
I know Brett's gonna do a deal.
We're up to $40,000.
That's really nice. Steady.
We're at $100,000 already.
Jimmy is so good at making a bribe
feel as visual as possible.
It's not just the counter going up,
it's also the cash piling up every second.
If you press the button right now,
you would get that pile of money.
$600,000.
How do you feel, Cory?
You're the one who has the least
amount of money out of us.
I mean, 720 grand...
That's a lot of money.
-Think it's gonna stop at a million?
-970!
-It could stop at a million.
-990!
Nobody's taking it.
One million dollars!
-Somebody pressed it.
-Yeah, Brett pressed it.
Congratulations, you're now a millionaire.
Brett, go to your money right now.
Come to your million dollars.
Come on in!
Brett played a good game.
-Brett, let's go smash your heart.
-Okay.
You wanna drop him with the bag?
Yeah, that, and then the guards
just start throwing them.
We're packing it as quickly as possible.
Seeing you jump in the money,
that must've been a surreal moment.
It was really cool.
I was really nervous about being here.
I don't wanna be on TV.
I had all these doubts.
And then I talked to my fiancée, she said,
"Be gone as long as you need to be."
"Just make it worth it."
And she supported me 100%.
So I got on the plane.
And then here we are, six weeks later,
and $1.2 million later.
It's so freaking cool.
-Let's do it.
Last game.
Just trying to make sure that this episode
finishes on time.
Here we go.
We gotta get the briefcases,
we gotta get the check.
Are you watching the finale
from last season?
Yeah, just seeing how we edited it.
Bring in the blindfolds!
Do you have any thoughts as you look back
on last year's finale?
I wonder what time we were filming.
That was like at 6:00 a.m.
I'm tired as hell.
How do you feel?
Final game, final episode.
We got two really good finalists.
I think we got great story,
two family men.
It's been a wild ride.
From the storm in Las Vegas,
to the City,
to the white room with the four games,
and the guy who tried to grab it
and missed it by inches,
to the thunderstorm
where we had to push a day,
and then we finally got our day
in the obstacle course
to going out to Fiji with Jeff Probst,
to coming back
and reintroducing the cubes,
to then doing the Strong Game
100 feet in the air,
something we've wanted to do forever,
then we have this massive Smart Game,
to burying 10 people at once
and doing a $1,000,000 bribe with them,
down to right here.
It's been a crazy 40-plus days
and Jon literally questioning everybody.
It's 4:00 a.m.
I really appreciate everyone continually
showing up with a smile on your face.
This is the schedule from tonight.
We're an hour behind
when the show was supposed to wrap.
I showed this to Jimmy,
and you know what he did
to this piece of paper?
Well, something like this?
-Yeah.
-That's pretty much what it is.
When we play the final game,
everyone will be gone?
Yeah. We're clearing everyone,
they got blindfolds.
And there's no one watching
the control room or anything?
I had them shut everything off.
We're right outside the control center,
and Jimmy was adamant
about cutting the feed
so not even the extended crew
knows who won.
All right, here we go.
One of you is not gonna have $5,000,000.
I promise you,
the other person understands,
if you win $5,000,000,
you go insane.
Lose your freaking mind.
Get them both to yell right before.
Right before, yeah.
To get the energy up, real quick,
I think we should all give a loud yell.
Three, two, one...
Let's go!
-That's good.
-There we go.
That was what we needed.
Yeah. That was great.
One of you is gonna be handed
this $5,000,000 check.
You can put it
in whatever briefcase you want,
and if either of you guesses correctly,
you are a multi-millionaire.
I need all our camera people
to turn around.
This is a battle between Cory and Tyler
and no one else on the planet.
All right, Jimmy.
-Am I good to turn around?
-You are.
Okay. Camera crew,
you can point the cameras over here.
Cory, turn around
and take the blindfold off.
What can you tell me about 9?
Is the check inside here?
Open it and find out.
I'm gonna go with 9.
Throw it off the stage.
We will be taking this briefcase
out of play.
Just cost me ten grand.
Cory is in possession
of the $5,000,000 check.
Now there's one less case.
Tyler, turn around.
Take off your blindfold.
-What about 2?
-Open it and find out.
He's deploying Tyler's strategy
back at him.
He's officially chosen 5!
There's no check.
So it has to be 6...
or 8.
I'm gonna go with 6.
Was it in this one?
-That'd be crazy, if so.
-Yeah, it is.
Really?
No shot. Are you joking?
It was in 8.
I was so close.
That just doesn't even feel real.
It's so crazy to only see
four briefcases on this table.
Is there $5,000,000 in that briefcase?
It's red! Oh, no!
Have you ever been on a shoot
this long in your life?
Believe it or not...
yes.
You're going with 3?
Wait, before you open it...
Get ready. Get ready, bro.
Did you hit it? Are you a millionaire?
Go to light.
Let's go!
Come on!
-You did it!
-Let's go!
You did it!
He hit it!
Oh, my God.
Get on the money!
All right, don't fall.
$5,000,000 Tyler just won,
and look at Cory.
Bro, you're literally standing
on your mountain of money.
Tyler, you just won Season 2
of Beast Games.
Tyler just won Season 2 of Beast Games
and $5,000,000!
Bro.
I can't wait to see
your wife and kids' reactions.
Man, I feel bad for Cory.
-I love you guys so much.
-I love you, Dad.
I'm really happy for Tyler.
If somebody could've won other than me,
I'm happy that it was him.
I'm gonna love the Lord
in the good times and the bad times.
Cory has officially been eliminated.
And this hurts.
All right, Russ, go for it.
Three, two, one, go!
We officially have a winner
of Season 2 of Beast Games!
Congratulations!
Congrats on winning Season 2!
Thank you so much for watching
all the way till the end.
I can't wait to see what you think
of Season 3.
I lost my voice.
-One more.
-Okay.
Tyler, just keep throwing up money
if you can.
And I can't wait to blow your mind
with Season 3.
Trust me, it's gonna be way better.
Look at the lighting and everything.
Oh, my God.
I feel on top of the world, man.
I lost my voice from yelling.
When I was serving a year in Korea
by myself,
I've missed out on half of my kids' lives.
Winning this just gives me a chance
to just be dad
and they don't have to worry
about when dad's coming back,
because my oldest is four
and he has a hard time when I leave.
And when my wife came to visit us
in the City,
she was telling me that
he was having a hard time
struggling without me there.
I don't want him to have to
experience that.
So I think I'll get out of the military,
we'll be able to retire,
and just spend time with our kids
and do what we want.
It's a dream come true.
I missed you guys so much.
Dada.
Jimmy, how are you gonna top this
for Season 3?
Don't you worry. I mean, you saw...
How do I have that much hair on my neck?
Congratulations!
They're all celebrating
that we just wrapped filming.
Do you get emotional at moments like this?
You just changed that guy's life.
I would be more emotional if I didn't
just film for 15 hours straight.
I'm struggling to keep my eyes open.
I'm worried in the cut
I'm gonna look sleepy.
Do you take a moment
to enjoy these milestones...
No, I'm about to fly to Africa tomorrow
to film a main channel video.
I don't even get half a day off
to celebrate.
We finished.
Tyler, we survived.
-Me Tyler?
-You Tyler.
No more casting other Tylers.
It's so confusing.
Can you take a moment
and enjoy this, Tyler, or...
No, I will enjoy this.
This is too big of a project
not to enjoy it.
He's gonna enjoy it by sleeping
for four days straight.
I'm gonna sleep for four days straight.
I'm very excited.
He's gonna sleep for four days,
enjoy it for a day,
and then start writing Season 3.
That and post as well.
Yeah, and how does this shot look?
Does it look insane?
Just sitting on $5,000,000
with this big frigging set.
Let me ask you...
This whole 10-episode series,
you've been asking me questions,
-let me ask you some.
-Hit me, Jimmy.
Do you think this will perform better
or worse than Season 1?
This? Yeah, of course.
I feel like everything was bigger
and more thought out.
And I personally got to know
the contestants even more.
I feel that's something that the viewers
will feel as well.
Yeah. I do too.
You guys poured a lot into this.
Yeah, you saw some days,
we had over 1,000 people working on it.
These are monster projects.
It's kind of funny
because I watch old interviews
I'd say stuff like, "In an optimal world,
if my eyes are open, I'm filming."
"Like, why would I not?"
And I see them, and I'm like, "Frig."
That's why I'm in this scenario right now.
Jimmy, I just want to say thank you.
Yeah, thank you.
Are you doing an outro to this?
I'll let you take it, man.
I'm so grateful for having us,
our entire crew,
you guys being so inclusive...
-Letting me document and capture.
-We didn't hide anything.
It'll be interesting to see
how it turns out.
But also subscribe to him.
He doesn't have a million subscribers.
It's kind of pissing me off.
He does like 3,000,000 views a video.
It doesn't make sense.
Thanks, Jimmy.
-Appreciate you having me, man.
-Yeah, thank you.
You've crushed it. Go back to your baby.
You're allowed to see your baby again.
-I love you, man.
-Bro.
I just want to say thank you all
before I head out.
Appreciate you guys. Turned out amazing.
Thank you.